

BERNARD SIN FAT

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

0410-819-165

bernardjbs@yahoo.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/bernard-sin-fat

https://github.com/bernardjbs

Perth - Western Australia

EDUCATION

Aug 2022 | UNIVERSITY OF WESTERN AUSTRALIA

Certificate | Full Stack Web Development

Apr 2002 | EDITH COWAN UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science | Computer Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- CS applied to JavaScript: OOP with JS, Data Structures, Algorithms
- Browser based technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive design, Bootstrap, Local storage
- Deployment/Command-line fundamentals: Heroku, Git, Github pages
- API Interaction: JSON, REST
- Databases: MySQL
- Server side development: Node.js, Express

SOFT SKILLS

- Multitasking able to handle several assignments
- Ability to prioritize independently but also a team player
- · Business aptitude skills
- Excellent research abilities
- Databases: MySQL
- Willing to stretch extra hours to complete assigned work
- Recognised for a strong work ethic, high standard and collaborative leadership

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer holding a Computer Science degree from ECU, a certificate in Full Stack development from UWA, and previous business owner with business management background. A key player transforming our photography family business from analog to digital, at a crucial time when digital photography was phasing out film and negative. Also, successfully built a picture and art framing business from scratch as an extension to the main family business. Currently a Chef at High on 55, a busy café situated on the iconic High Street in Fremantle. For the past few years, I have been helping them maintain a 5 star rating on TripAdvisor and Facebook, as well as a score of 4.7 on the Google rating. With my attributes acquired through my experience, I am confident to adapt and integrate new environments.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER - INTERN

Nano Solutions - Aug 2022 ~ Present

- PHP fundamentals with Laravel and Homestead as VM using MVC pattern
- · Git branching
- · Application testing
- JavaScript and VueJS

WEB DEVELOPER - JUNIOR

BAM Creative - Jun 2005 ~ Sep 2005

- Database design and implementation with MySQL
- Back and front end programming using PHP, HTML and CSS
- Liaising with customers via phone, email or personally to report work progress and milestone achieved to their satisfaction

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

CHEF

High on 55 Café - Five star ranking in Food on TripAdvisor and Facebook, scored 4.7 in the Google rating system | Nov 2017 ~ Present

- · Sustaining the restaurant's outstanding reputation by ensuring consistently good quality meals.
- Drive the cost efficiency through managing ingredient supply and inventory
- Conduct the end-to-end process of made-to-order breakfast and Asian-inspired lunch

BUSINESS OWNER

Sin Fat Studio - Mauritius - Dec 2005 ~ Sep 2012

The main family business. We take portrait photographs and run a photo lab. As a computer graduate, I went back to help my family computerise the business and digitalise the photo lab, at the risk of the business fading away due to the shift from negative to digital printing. We are now fully digitalised and up to date with market demand. It was an important decision to leave my pursue in software development career, but it was worth it.

BUSINESS OWNER

Pictura Frames - Mauritius - Sep 2012 ~ Apr 2016

An expansion of the family business to produce high quality picture and art frames, both on production and custom made. I built the company from scratch, importing the machinery from South Africa and supply materials from UK, China and Malaysia. I managed production and sales. The business is still running at present.